https://koolpak.com/privacy-statement/

Log in
Lost your password?
Remember me
No account yet?
Create an Account
Search for:
PRIVACY STATEMENT
Your privacy is important to Kool Pak®.  This privacy statement provides information about the personal information that Kool Pak® collects, and the ways in which Kool Pak® uses that personal information.
Personal information collection
Kool Pak, Inc may collect and use the following kinds of personal information:
[information about your use of this website]
[information that you provide using for the purpose of registering with the website]
[information about transactions carried out over this website ]
[information that you provide for the purpose of subscribing to the website services ]
[any other information that you send to Kool Pak, Inc.]
Using personal information
Kool Pak®  may use your personal information to:
[administer this website;]
[personalize the website for you;]
[enable your access to and use of the website services;]
[publish information about you on the website;]
[send to you products that you purchase;]
[supply to you services that you purchase;]
[send to you statements and invoices;]
[collect payments from you; and]
[send you marketing communications.]
WhereKool Pak® discloses your personal information to its agents or sub-contractors for these purposes, the agent or sub-contractor in question will be obligated to use that personal information in accordance with the terms of this privacy statement.
In addition to the disclosures reasonably necessary for the purposes identified elsewhere above, Kool Pak® may disclose your personal information to the extent that it is required to do so by law, in connection with any legal proceedings or prospective legal proceedings, and in order to establish, exercise or defend its legal rights.
Securing your data
Kool Pak® will take reasonable technical and organizational precautions to prevent the loss, misuse or alteration of your personal information.
Kool Pak® will store all the personal information you provide [on its secure servers].
[Information relating to electronic transactions entered into via this website will be protected by encryption technology.]
Cross-border data transfers
Information thatKool Pak® collects may be stored and processed in and transferred between any of the countries in whichKool Pak® operates to enable the use of the information in accordance with this privacy policy.
[In addition, personal information that you submit for publication on the website will be published on the internet and may be available around the world.]
You agree to such cross-border transfers of personal information.
Updating this statement
Kool Pak® may update this privacy policy by posting a new version on this website.
You should check this page occasionally to ensure you are familiar with any changes.
Other websites
This website contains links to other websites.
Kool Pak® is not responsible for the privacy policies or practices of any third party.
ContactKool Pak®
If you have any questions about this privacy policy orKool Pak® treatment of your personal information, please write:
by email to [EMAIL ADDRESS]; or
by post to [POSTAL ADDRESS].
Credit
Privacy statement created using Contractology http://www.contractology.com.
Scroll To Top
